本字幕由YYeTs字幕組原創翻譯
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息
饑餓
的青春
第二季  第十集
《饑餓的青春》前情提要
Previously on Young & Hungry.
我愛你
I love you.
你怎么知道誰是真命天子
How do you know which one is the one?
很簡單  是吻
It's simple. It's the kiss.
庫珀搬到樓上了  現在我"樓下"開始
Cooper moved in upstairs, and now I'm starting
對喬什有感覺了
to feel things for Josh downstairs.
媽呀
Oh, my damn.
喬什  是你
Josh... it's you.
加比  在你被喬什的"我愛你"迷惑前
Gabi, before you fall for Josh's big "I love you,"
你該知道他三個月前就覺得自己愛你了
You should know that he thought he loved you three months ago.
然后  當他改變了主意
And then when he changed his mind,
又說服所有人騙你
convinced everyone to lie to you about it.
-是真的嗎  -加比  一切我都能解釋
- Is that true? - Gabi, I can explain everything.
-天啊  是真的  -加比  等等
- Oh my god, it is true. - Gabi, wait.
不  你給我讓開
No, get the hell away from me.
加比  你在嗎
Gabi, are you in here?
該死  天啊
Damn it. Oh, my god!
別這樣嚇我  我差點揍你了
Don't scare me like that! I almost went Lil' So-so on your ass.
加比  我們得談談  我給你發了一千條短信
Gabi, we need to talk. I sent you, like, a thousand texts.
這是雪上加霜
Well, then you added insult to injury
因為我沒有不限量短信套餐
because I don't have unlimited texting.
加比  我一知道喬什喜歡你
Gabi, I wanted to tell you about Josh
就想跟你說
the second that I found out.
但你好像和庫珀很開心
But you seemed so happy with Cooper,
我就是不忍心告訴你[沒有心]
I just-- I didn't have the heart.
你承認自己沒良心啦
So you admit you have no heart.
你有權對我生氣  好嗎
Look, you have every right to be mad at me. Okay?
雖然我的本意是好的
Even though my intentions were good,
這很愚蠢  我負全責
it was stupid and I take full responsibility.
也許你該為你的行為
And maybe you should take some responsibility
負一些責
for how you've been acting.
什么
What?
你該為你的行為
You should take some responsibility
負一些責
for how you've been acting.
我的行為嗎
How I've been acting?
我愛喬什  不  我愛庫珀
"I love Josh. No, I love Cooper.
他是真命天子  不  他才是
"He's the one. No, he's the one.
我有兩個真命天子
I have two ones."
首先  那一點也不像我
Okay, first of all, that sounds nothing like me.
其次
And second of all-- -
你得趕走門口那個人
you need to get rid of whoever is at that door.
好吧  從現在開始我挺你
Okay. From now on, I got your back.
-她在嗎  -不在
- Is she here? - Nope!
-我知道她在  -你怎么知道的
- I know she's here. - How?
我看見她了
I see her.
-加比  我們得談談  -不談  不要鬧劇了
- Gabi, we need to talk. - No. No more talking, no more drama.
我需要的是讓今晚結束
What I need is for this night to end.
那可不是結束的聲音
That is not the sound of ending!
-加比  我們得談談  -三個月來
- Gabi, we need to talk. - For three months,
你們一句話都沒跟我說  現在你倆閉不了嘴了
none of you said a word to me. And now none of you can shut up!
聽到了嗎  庫珀
You hear that, Cooper?
她不想跟你說話  拜拜了您啊
She doesn't want to talk to you. So buh-bye now.
去你的  拜拜了您啊
Don't buh-bye me. Buh-bye you.
-后退  -你才后退
- Hey, back off. - You back off.
你倆什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you two?
對不起  我過分了
I'm sorry, that was out of line.
是的
It was.
-這樣也是  -搞什么
- So is this. - What the hell?
喬什  住手
Josh, stop!
好吧  夠了
Okay, that's it.
你們快住手
Oh my god, you guys, stop!
-不要弄壞攪拌機  -天啊
- Not the blender! - Oh, my god!
住手  住手  住手
Stop! Stop! Stop!
別弄倒燭臺
Not the votives!
住手
Stop!
天啊  你們得停止打架  好嗎
Oh, my god! Okay, you need to stop fighting, all right?
因為你們打得太挫了  好丟人
Because you're bad at it, and it's embarrassing!
我受不了了  好嗎
I can't take this anymore. Okay?
我受夠了  你倆我都受夠了
I'm-- I'm done. I'm done with both of you.
好嗎  你們得出去
All right? You need to get out.
明天上班時見嗎
So I'll see you at work tomorrow?
是的  但我會遲到的
Yes, but I will be late.
翻譯  冰藍  阿包  roaddog
校對  roaddog
時間軸  阿包
后期  冰藍   總監  roaddog
醒醒  加比
Wake up, Gabi,
你最好的朋友要帶你去吃早餐...
'cause your best friend is taking you to breakfast at--
早上好
Good morning!
你看起來精力充沛  怎么了
You seem peppy. Why?
因為那些謊言和背叛  我睡不著
Well, thanks to all the lies and betrayal, I couldn't sleep.
所以我出去散了個步
So I took one of those
想著我這輩子都干了些啥啊
"What am I doing with my life" walks,
我意識到你說得對
and I realized you were right.
我表現得像是浪漫喜劇里為情所困的姑娘
I've been acting like some lovesick girl in a rom-com
而沒有追逐我的夢想
instead of following my dreams.
我不是茱莉亞·羅伯茨  而是茱莉亞·蔡爾德
I'm not Julia Roberts, I'm Julia Child.
然后突然想到  達比
And then it hit me. D'arby.
聲音很尖的流浪漢嗎
The homeless guy with the really high-pitched voice?
不  那是達布尼
No, no, no, that's Dabney.
我說的是查爾斯·達比
I'm talking about Charles D'arby,
舊金山最有名的廚師
One of the most famous chefs in San Francisco.
每年他都會舉辦一場比賽  尋找一名學徒
Every year, he has a contest to find an apprentice to work
在他瑞士的米其林星級餐廳工作  我申請了
at his Michelin-starred restaurant in Switzerland, and I applied!
"你和喬什的工作呢"  你問
"What about your job with Josh," You ask?
我先去上班  直到我得到學徒的工作
Well, I'm keeping it until I get the apprenticeship,
我會得到的
and I am getting it.
我已經提交了三份原創食譜
I already submitted three original recipes,
個人情況說明
a personal statement,
和三封偽造的推薦信
and three fake references.
我只用拍一段刀工的視頻了
All I have left to do is make a video of my knife skills.
我喝了好多咖啡啊
Man, I've had a lot of coffee.
-親愛的  真抱歉  -沒必要
- Baby, I am so sorry. - Not necessary.
我再也不氣你對我撒謊喬什的事了
I am no longer angry with you for lying to me about Josh.
因為你是被他強迫騙我的
Because you were coerced by him into deceiving me.
艾略特  我原諒你
And Elliot, I forgive you
因為你并沒有背叛我
because you didn't really betray me as a friend
畢竟你一開始就不怎么喜歡我
since you never really liked me in the first place.
太對了
That is so true.
關鍵是...
The important thing is...
我要結婚了  而你不在賓客名單上
I'm getting married, and you're not invited.
棒棒噠
Yay!
加比來了嗎
Did I hear Gabi?
尤蘭達  能讓我們單獨待一會嗎
Hey, Yolanda, um, would you mind giving us a minute?
喬什  別這樣  我不想討論這事
Josh, no, I don't want to talk.
尤蘭達  作為我的朋友  請你留下
Yolanda, as my friend, I'm asking you to stay.
-沒問題  -尤蘭達  作為你的老板
- Oh, sure. - Yolanda, as your boss,
請你離開
I'm asking you to leave.
-好的  -你欠我的
- Yep. - You owe me.
-對  -我可是付工資給你的人
- Yep. - I pay you.
抱歉  加比  錢更重要
Sorry, Gabi, monies before honeys.
加比  我們得談談
Gabi, we need to talk.
是啊  早餐你想吃什么
Yes, we do. What would you like for breakfast?
我想來一份美味的
I would like a delicious plate
"請坐下來  聽聽這個"
of please sit down and listen to this.
-喬什  -我就想讓你
- Josh! - Look, it's just a voice mail
聽一通語音留言  僅此而已
I want you to hear. That's it.
好吧
Fine.
昨晚在我取消婚禮之后
Last night after I called off my wedding,
我想見的人是你
you're the person that I wanted to see.
我甚至去你家  拿著玫瑰跑上逃生梯
I even ran up your fire escape with roses.
我不知道該說什么
Um, I don't know what I was gonna say,
但知道我想見你
but I knew that I needed to see you
然后我看到了庫珀和你在一起
and then I saw Cooper and you,
要是你和庫珀在一起很幸福
and look, if you're happy with Cooper,
就當沒收到過這條消息
just disregard this whole message.
但要是你覺得或許和我在一起會更幸福的話
But if you think you might, like, be happier with me,
給我回電  另外  我是喬什
call me back. This is Josh, by the way.
天吶  喬什
Oh, my God. Josh.
我知道  很情真意切吧
I know. Pretty intense.
你真的留了那通留言嗎
Did you really leave me that message?
當然
Sure did.
我能問你點事嗎
Can I ask you something?
-問吧  -為什么我從來沒有收到過呢
- Anything. - How come I never got it?
這個問題問得好
Well, good question.
還有  為什么我的語音消息會在你電腦里呢
And, uh, how come my message is on your computer?
又是一個好問題
Another good question.
會不會是因為你開始和別的人約會
Is it possible that you tricked me into giving you my phone,
所以你騙我  讓我把手機給你
so that you could delete the message before I got it
這樣一來  你就能在我看到前把它刪了
because you started dating someone new?
什么
What?
猜得有點兒對
That's a little bit of a reach.
加比  我...我看到你和庫珀在一起
Gabi, I-- I saw you with Cooper.
我不想破壞你的生活
I didn't want to screw up your life.
是啊  那時你和吉莉在一起
Yeah, well, you were with Jilly,
或許你只是不想破壞你自己的生活
so maybe you just didn't want to screw up your own life.
現在  早餐你想吃什么
Now, what do you want for breakfast?
我想聽到你說"我們在一起吧"
What I want is to hear you say we're gonna be together.
-不可能  -為什么  你還和庫珀在一起嗎
- No! - Why, you're staying with Cooper?
天吶  不  喬什...
Oh, my God! No, Josh...
我受不了了  好嗎  我辭職
I can't take this. Okay? I quit.
-什么  -我忍不下去了
- What? - I can't do this anymore.
好嗎  我受不了每天來上班
Okay? I can't come to work
都要和你進行一番這樣的對話
and go through this with you every single day!
加比  你不能辭職
Gabi, you can't quit.
你打算做什么
What are you gonna do?
告訴你吧
Well, for your information,
我要給非常著名的查爾斯·達比大廚
I have an apprenticeship with the very famous
當學徒
Chef Charles D'arby.
真的嗎
You do?
其實還算不上學徒
Well, it's-- it's not so much an apprenticeship
只參加一場學徒面試
as it is an audition for an apprenticeship.
-是嗎  -其實還沒參加面試
- It is? - Well, it's-- it's not so much an audition
只申請參加了招收學徒的
as it is an application for an audition
面試活動
that could lead to an apprenticeship.
所以你還沒當上
So you have nothing?
我本可以騙你說我當上了
Well, I could've lied and said I had something,
但我可不像你  喬什
but I'm not you, Josh.
再見
Goodbye.
華夫餅  我該說早餐想吃華夫餅的
Waffles. I should have said I wanted waffles for breakfast.
加比  你在外面干什么
Gabi, what are you doing out here?
我在等面試資格的通知
I'm waiting to hear if I got the audition.
我的手機信號只有在這里才滿格
And this is the only place where I get full bars.
-達布尼  -你好
- Oh! Hey, Dabney - Hi!
我在網上看了當學徒的要求
So, you know, I was reading about that apprenticeship online.
我沒想到得到一個面試的機會是這么難
And I didn't realize how hard it was to get an audition.
-索菲亞  我會得到的  -當然
- Sofia, I'm going to get this. - Oh, no, of course. No.
我完全相信你會的
I 1000% believe you will get this.
但萬一沒成  也沒有那么糟
But, um, in case you don't, it's not the end of the world.
懂嗎  你仍然可以在喬什那里上班
You know? You still have your job at Josh's.
-我辭職了  -什么
- I quit Josh's. - What?
我知道這很瘋狂
I know, it seems crazy.
但經歷了這一切之后
But the thought of working for him
為他工作感覺太怪了
after everything we've been though seems just as crazy.
好吧  你確定嗎  因為你好像
Okay, are you sure? Because you have, like,
根本沒有機會參加那場高級面試
zero percent chance of getting that fancy apprenticeship.
你剛剛才說你相信我的實力
Hey! You just said that you believed in me!
天吶  我們得靠賣頭發付房租了
Oh, my God, we're gonna have to sell our hair to pay rent!
來電話了
It's ringing!
-是組委會  -打開揚聲器
- It's them. - Put it on speaker.
好的
Okay.
喂
Hello?
戴蒙德小姐  我是達比大廚
Miss Diamond, this is Chef D'arby.
達比大廚  我是戴蒙德小姐
Chef D'arby, this is Miss Diamond.
你被選中參加我的學徒面試了
You have been chosen to audition for my apprenticeship.
明早九點整  希望你準時出席
We'll expect to see you tomorrow at 9:00 a.m. sharp.
天吶  我會準時到的  非常感謝
Oh, my God. I will be there. Thank you so much!
我知道你能行的
I knew you'd get it!
祝賀你
Congratulations!
謝謝  達布尼
Thanks, Dabney!
天吶  我的媽呀
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God!
冷靜  這時候得集中思想
Okay, settle down. It's time to focus.
我會的  索菲亞  看看這個地方
I am focused. Sofia, look at this place.
那位是達比大廚
That's Chef D'arby.
英國人就是會長啊
They sure know how to grow them in England.
"拜托  先生  能再給我點嗎"
Please sir, can I have some more?
《霧都孤兒》經典臺詞
-你能行的  -好的
- Look, you can do this. - Okay.
-祝你好運  -謝謝
- Good luck. - Thanks.
達比大廚  我是加比·戴蒙德
Oh, Chef D'arby, I'm Gabi Diamond.
謝謝你給我這次機會
Thank you so much for this opportunity.
占我便宜的機會嗎
The opportunity to touch me inappropriately?
抱歉  聽著  我就一個小問題
Oh, sorry. Uh, listen, I just had a quick question.
是什么讓我進面試的
What was it that actually got me the audition?
我的菜譜嗎  還是我的刀工
Was it my recipes? Was it my knife skills?
實際上  是卡明斯基先生
Actually, it was Mr. Kaminski.
-你幫我進的面試嗎  -不用謝
- You got me this audition? - You're welcome.
-你好大的膽子  -我以為你想進啊
- How could you? - I thought that's what you wanted.
不  我想的是靠自己進
No! What I wanted was to do it myself.
我是想幫你實現你的夢想
Look, I was just trying to help you get your dream.
沒錯  喬什  我的夢想
Yeah, exactly, Josh. My dream. Mine.
我以為自己是在做好事
I thought I was doing something nice.
拜托  你就是想贏回我罷了
Please, you were just trying to win me back!
真的嗎  這聽著像是個好計劃嗎
Really? Does that sound like a good plan?
幫你拿到在瑞士的學徒資格
To help you get an internship in Switzerland
好讓你離開我半年嗎
that takes you away from me for six months?
-這怎么就能贏回你了  -我不知道  喬什
- How is that getting you back? - I don't know, Josh.
但你做的所有事都讓我覺得
But all you've done is made me realize
我不該在這里
that I'm not supposed to be here.
各位  各就各位
Everybody, take your places.
我們要開始了
We are about to begin.
我做的就是幫你拿到面試資格
Look, all I did was get you the audition.
贏不贏就看你自己了
It's up to you to win it.
你們要做的菜是
And the dish you will be preparing is...
波爾多紅酒醬汁森林牛排
filet de boeuf forestiere with bordelaise sauce
配小土豆[法語]
and petit gratin dauphinois.
-你們有兩個小時  -光翻這話就得兩小時吧
- You have two hours. - I need two hours to translate that.
芮娜德小姐  你的紅酒醬汁
Now, Ms. Renard, the bordelaise ?
你的  哈珀先生
You, Mr. Harper.
到你了  戴蒙德小姐
On to you, Miss Diamond.
濃稠度有點問題哈
Bit of a consistency problem there.
我能補救的  可以的
Well, I can fix it, I can fix it.
行了  戴蒙德小姐  你走吧
It's over, Miss Diamond. Off you go!
什么  我走吧  我走吧
What? Off I go? Off I go?
我走了
Off I go...
走開
Go away!
庫珀
Oh. Cooper.
別生氣
Don't be upset.
我就是來拿自己東西  把鑰匙還給你
I just came to grab my stuff, drop off your key.
我不是批評你
Not to be judgey,
但你鼻子上那白色東西是什么
but what is the white stuff under your nose?
是我最愛的毒品  糖霜
It's my drug of choice: frosting.
-你還好嗎  -是啊  不能再糟了
- Are you okay? - Oh, yeah. Never worse.
-你呢  -我女朋友和我最好的朋友都跑了
- How are you? - Well, I lost my girlfriend and my best friend.
那兩個都是你
Those are both you, by the way.
庫珀  真的很抱歉最后事情成這樣
Cooper, I'm... I'm so sorry for the way things ended.
不  加比  是我很抱歉
No, Gabi, I'm sorry.
你那么棒
You're amazing.
知道嗎  你像是在這里
You know, you're, like, up here.
而我在這里
And I'm down here.
像我這樣的人永遠追不到你那么好的姑娘
And a guy down here never gets the girl up here.
所以當我發現喬什對你有感覺
So when I found out Josh had feelings for you,
我慌了
I panicked.
覺得如果你知道了  我會失去你
I thought if you found out, I'd lose you.
-庫珀  你不用跟我說這些  -我要說
- Cooper, you don't have to tell me all this. - Yes, I do.
我可以接受我們不在一起
I can accept us not being together,
不能接受的是我在KTV的表現
what I can't accept is the way I acted at the karaoke bar.
我想要你知道我比那樣要好
I need you to know that I'm better than that.
你當然好了
Of course you are.
如果不是  那我也不可能愛上你
If you weren't, then I wouldn't have fallen in love with you.
我也從來沒有要存心傷害你
And I never meant to hurt you.
我知道
I know.
你額頭上也有糖霜
Frosting's up there, too.
為什么
Why?
你好啊  索菲亞
Oh! Hey, Sofia.
我就是隨手做個
I'm just whipping up a little midnight snack
波爾多紅酒醬汁森林牛排
of filet de boeuf forestiere with bordelaise sauce
配小土豆當宵夜
and petit gratin dauphinois.
為什么
Why?
因為我的實力不止面試那樣  索菲亞
Because I'm better than that audition, Sofia.
是因為庫珀
It's because of Cooper.
他即使知道我們不會復合
Even though he knew we weren't gonna get back together,
也還是想要挽回印象
he still wanted to redeem himself.
我也要對達比大廚這么做
And that's what I have to do with Chef D'arby.
拿不到學徒資格我無所謂
I'm fine with not getting the apprenticeship.
有所謂的是達比大廚只因為我的
What I'm not fine with is Chef D'arby only remembering me
-爛醬汁記住了我  -親愛的
- for my ploppy sauce. - Oh, sweetie.
我肯定他根本沒想過你
I'm sure he's barely thought about you at all.
他會記住我的  好嗎
Well, he's going to remember me, okay?
我得不到工作  但還是能贏回名聲
I didn't get the job, but I can get my reputation back.
這一次  我的牛肉要燥翻天
And this time, my boeuf will raise the roof.
如果你還能再見到他  給他我電話
Well, if you're gonna see him again, give him my number.
我想嘗嘗他的"肉"
I'd like a bite of his boeuf.
達比大廚  抱歉打擾你
Chef D'arby, I'm really sorry to interrupt.
我能冒昧問下大師在做什么佳肴嗎
Oh, may I ask what amazing dish the maestro is preparing?
雞蛋
Eggs.
聽著  我知道我的醬汁在該
Well, listen, I know my sauce went plop-plop
絲般順滑的時候成了團
when it should have gone whoosh.
我也不指望您能改變主意
And I don't expect you to change your mind,
但我不能接受自己明顯沒盡力的作品
but I couldn't live with myself knowing I didn't do my best work.
所以請允許我呈現
So, may I now present...
波爾多紅酒醬汁森林牛排
filet de boeuf forestiere with bordelaise sauce
配小土豆
and petit gratin dauphinois.
絲般順滑
Whoosh.
我希望這頭牛的死法
I hope this cow was slaughtered more humanely
能比你說出的那些法語更人道
than how you just slaughtered the French language.
是法語啊
Oh, it's French!
不錯
Well done.
在我辦比賽的十年里
In the ten years since I've had this competition,
沒一個選手有勇氣
not a single contestant has had the courage
能再來找我證明自己
to try and redeem themselves with me.
說真的  達比大廚  我這樣不是為了你
Well, honestly, Chef D'arby, I didn't do it for you.
-是為我自己  -我很佩服
- I did it for me. - Well, I'm impressed.
希望明年能見到你  戴蒙德大廚
I hope to see you again next year, Chef Diamond.
你是剛喊我大廚嗎
Did you just call me chef?
我是大廚了  我是大廚了
I'm a chef, I'm a chef!
-不許抱我  -我們求異存同嘛
- No hugging. - Disagree to disagree.
-加比  -謝謝你
- Gabi. - Thank you.
-什么  -我之前很氣你干預我的生活
- What? - I was so mad at you for meddling in my life,
我該只說謝謝你就好的
and I should've just said thank you.
-你是拿到學徒資格了嗎  -不是
- So, you got the apprenticeship? - Not even close.
不過多虧了你  我有了失敗的機會
But thanks to you, I got the chance to fail,
也讓我有了
which gave me the chance
振作起來  向查爾斯·達比證明
to pick myself up and prove to Charles D'arby
自己當得起"大廚"名號的機會
that I'm worthy of the title chef.
挺好的
Good for you.
你還專程來說謝謝真是很好
It was nice of you to come by and say thanks...
等等  還有呢
Wait. Wait, wait. There's more.
說到了第二次機會  不如你也給我一個吧
In the spirit of second chances, how about you give me one?
喬什  我真的很想做你的...
Josh, I really wanna be your--
-女朋友  -大廚
- Girlfriend. - Chef.
沒錯  大廚
Yes, chef.
你要再做我大廚我很歡迎
I would love to have you as my chef again.
-我好像聽到了"女朋友"  -你聽到了嗎
- I think I heard "girlfriend." - Did you hear that?
我還想你說的"大廚"聲音夠大
I was hoping you said chef loud enough
然后只聽成了"大廚朋友"呢
so all you heard was "chef-friend."
喬什  我們之間的感覺的確無法否認
Listen, Josh, what we have between us is undeniable.
但也瘋狂  混亂又讓人迷惑
But it's also crazy and messy and confusing--
-跟我約一次會吧  -什么
- Go on a date with me. - What?
加比  我們經歷了那么多事
Gabi, you and I have been through so much,
但卻從沒有簡單的約過一次會
but the one thing we've never done is go on a simple date.
所以...你愿意嗎
So... will you?
就算你拒絕  我還是用你的
Look, you're still gonna have a job even if you say no.
但我覺得我們之間也值得有第二次機會
But I think you and I deserve a second chance, too.
你這是答應還是...
Is that a yes or...?
這是個有答應趨勢的感嘆
It's a "huh" with "yes" tendencies.
好  那我們今晚在艾略特和埃蘭的訂婚派對見吧
Okay. I'll see you tonight at Elliot and Alan's engagement party?
-沒問題  -之后帶你去吃晚餐
- Absolutely. - Take you to dinner afterwards?
我會考慮的
I will think about it.
今晚見
I'll see you tonight.
她會考慮的
She's gonna think about it!
-我看起來怎么樣  -美翻了
- How do I look? - Amazing!
我們絕對是那個基佬訂婚派對上
I'm pretty sure we're gonna be the two cutest girls
最美的兩個姑娘
at that gay engagement party.
我很高興事情是這么發展的
You know, I'm really happy about the way this all turned out.
那句話說得真對
I think it's really true,
當上帝關上了一扇門  會打開一扇窗
when god closes a door, he opens a window.
-喂  -戴蒙德小姐  我是達比大廚
- Hello? - Miss Diamond, this is Chef D'arby.
達比大廚  你好  有事嗎
Chef D'arby? Oh, hello, what can I do for you?
我發現比賽的
It has come to my attention
冠軍是作弊贏得的資格
that the winner of the competition cheated.
她提前知曉了試菜內容
She found out the audition dish in advance.
通常  我會把機會給第二名
Normally, I'd offer the position to the first runner-up,
但我對你印象深刻
but I was so impressed by you,
決定把學徒機會給你
I've decided to offer you the apprenticeship.
-真的嗎  -我知道時間倉促
- Really? - I know this is short notice,
但我們希望你能連夜飛來蘇黎世
but we need you on the red eye to Zurich tonight.
周一早上我們廚房見
I'm expecting you in the kitchen Monday morning.
恭喜你  大廚
Congratulations, Chef.
謝謝  謝謝  謝謝
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
-天啊  -天啊  你成功了
- Oh, my god! - Oh, my god! You did it!
我成功了
I did it!
等等  喬什怎么辦
Wait, wait, wait. What about Josh?
-學徒資格怎么辦  -喬什  學徒
- What about the apprenticeship? - Oh! Josh, the apprenticeship.
喬什  學徒  我怎么突然有這么多選擇了
Josh, the apprenticeship. How do I suddenly have so many options?
上帝打開了那么多窗戶干嘛
God opened too many windows. Why did you open so many windows?
我要怎么辦  索菲亞
What am I gonna do, Sofia?
茱莉亞會怎么做
What would Julia do?
茱莉亞·羅伯茨還是蔡爾德
Roberts or Child?
蔡爾德  做菜的那個
Child. Child! The one who cooks!
我一定很愛這男人  因為我戴著領結呢
I must really love this man 'cause I'm wearing a bow tie.
我一定很愛這男人
And I must really love this man
因為我居然在KTV辦訂婚派對
because I'm having my engagement party at a karaoke bar.
親愛的  誰定了鐵板燒啊
Oh, damn, baby, who ordered the fajitas?
-因為你真是帥到冒煙  -謝謝
- 'Cause you are sizzling hot. - Thank you.
我真沒想到能有這一天
I never thought I'd see the day.
你可能跟加比去約會
You may be going on a date with Gabi,
艾略特要結婚了
Elliot getting married,
而我...孑然一身
and here I am... with nothing.
我在吧臺那掛著賬呢
I have a tab open at the bar.
除了那個
Except that.
加比
未接來電  加比
喬什  我打來是因為有事要說
Hey, Josh. I'm calling because I have some news.
超級棒的事
Some really amazing news.
我拿到學徒資格了
I got the apprenticeship.
我真的很想當面告訴你
I hate to tell you this over the phone,
但如果看到了你
but if I saw you in person,
我怕自己做不出這樣的決定了
I'm not sure I'd be able to make the same decision.
在經歷了這瘋狂的一周
After this crazy week of deciding
覺得選庫珀還是你以后
whether I should choose Cooper or choose you,
我決定選自己
I decided to choose me.
這是我做過最艱難的決定了
And it's the hardest decision that I've ever had to make.
真的很抱歉我們沒能有第二次機會
I'm really sorry we didn't get a second chance.
希望你諒解
I hope you understand.
你一直支持著我  我知道你還會的
You've always been there for me, so I know that you will.
我會給你們寄明信片的  再見
Okay, I'll send you guys a postcard. Bye!
另外  我是加比
Oh, this is Gabi, by the way.
太讓人傷心了  達布尼
It's just sad, Dabney.
加比才走了幾天  日子好難過
Gabi's only been gone a few days and it's just really hard.
我在公寓里亂溜達  吃麥片
You know, I rattle around the apartment, eat cereal.
之前我們形影不離
We used to do everything together.
購物  美甲  叫外賣
Shop, get pedicures, order takeout.
你知道最糟的是什么嗎
You know what the worst part is?
她帶走了平板電腦  我只能用筆記本了
She took the tablet so I'm stuck using the laptop.
真討厭  你懂嗎
It just really sucks. You know what I mean?
我的狗讓我燒東西
My dog tells me to burn stuff.
聊天真愉快
Good talk.